

Dolzhit Tsyrendorzhieva

FRONT END DEVELOPER









ABOUT ME

Hi! I am Front End Developer experienced in creating apps with React, Redux, TypeScript. I'm planning to upgrade my skills further with Node JS and become full-stack developer. In spare time I like doing projects with new technologies to impove skills and expand knowledge. Ready to consider full-time employment as well as project work.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

09.2021 - present

FREELANCE

- Development of SPA using react, redux, reactrouter-dom, redux-thunk, axios, formik, material UI, styled components.
- Refactoring, bug fixing, migrating to TypeScript.
- Creation of reusable components.
- Development using unit tests and integrational tests with storybook and jest.

RETAIL MANAGER

2011 - 2019

NOETY LTD

- Staff supervision
- Dealing with customer queries and complaints
- Overseeing pricing and stock control

EDUCATION

IT - INCUBATOR

2021

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Front end development. React / Redux / TypeScript

UDEMY

2020

IMTP, Moscow

2003 - 2008

WEB DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP

Web developement - HTML, CSS, JS. By Colt Steele

SECIALIST IN LAW

Specialist with knowledge of foreign languages.

CONTACT

+7 977 862 3028

dolzhit.ts@gmail.com

zillomoons.github.io

Moscow, Russian Federation

SKILLS

- React / Redux
- Redux-Thunk / Redux-Saga
- TypeScript / JavaScript
- REST API / HTTP / HTTPS / Axios
- Unit tests / Storybook / Postman
- React-Router-Dom
- Formik
- HTML5 / CSS3
- Styled Components / Material UI
- Git / Github

LANGUAGES

- English: upper intermediate (in progress)
- Russian: native speaker